<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <!-- INCIFOR MiniScreen0 -->
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_0_paragraph0">The DNA of all human beings is 99.6% identical, but the information contained in that unique 0.4% is essential for obtaining important answers. In Spain, nearly 9,000 bodies have been recovered from more than 700 mass graves that have been excavated. The work of identifying the remains, carried out through genetic genealogy, is essential to bring closure to the families of the missing.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_1_paragraph0">Between 30 and 50% of fatal traffic accidents involve individuals who were driving under the influence of alcohol. In these cases, it is very important to determine whether a person\'s actions were influenced by the presence of drugs in their system.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_2_paragraph0">Improvements in the processes and instruments used by forensic science have led to a huge qualitative leap in the resolution of legal issues. From genetic tests that determine kinship to DNA samples that prove the perpetrator of a crime. From the presence of toxins in violent crimes to the first step in addressing the situation of a drug addict. Forensic science has a direct and clear impact on people in such fundamental aspects of their lives as honour, justice and death.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_3_paragraph0">With the aim of serving as a centre of reference in teaching and research, as well as advising the Administration of Justice, the ‘Luís Concheiro’ Institute of Forensic and Criminological Sciences (INCIFOR) has been created, whose areas of expertise are Legal Medicine, Toxicology and Criminology.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_4_paragraph0">The “Luís Concheiro” Institute of Forensic and Criminological Sciences (INCIFOR) offers a wide portfolio of services that are available to both public and private organizations.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_5_paragraph0">"The Luis Concheiro Institute of Forensic and Criminological Sciences (INCIFOR) (formerly the Institute of Legal Medicine), based in Santiago de Compostela, is a mixed institution of international renown in the fields of legal medicine, toxicology, and forensic genetics. "</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_6_paragraph0">"It was created by Decree (Galician) 247/1992, of July 30, following an agreement between the University of Santiago de Compostela (USC) and the Regional Government of Galicia, although it has been conducting research and providing services since 1978. "</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_7_paragraph0">The Institute, whose headquarters are located in the historic building of the Faculty of Medicine in Santiago de Compostela, actively participates in the training of students in Medicine, Law, Criminology, and Pharmacy, among others, as well as students in various master\'s programmes. \n\nIt is responsible for the USC Doctorate programme ‘Advances and New Strategies in Forensic Sciences’. It also collaborates with various national and international universities in the undergraduate and postgraduate training of their students.\n</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_8_paragraph0">INCIFOR also participates in training activities for Justice Administration personnel and serves as a reference centre for internships in its Toxicology and Forensic Genetics laboratories for criminology students and vocational training students.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_9_paragraph0">INCIFOR carries out extensive expert work in the field of Forensic Genetics and Toxicology under the annual agreement between the USC and the Regional Government of Galicia. It works closely with the Courts of Justice and State security forces. It has signed agreements and contracts with various public and private administrations to carry out analyses and other expert activities.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_10_paragraph0">"Its extensive research capacity has enabled it to develop and implement advanced methods of genetic analysis and toxicological analysis in its daily activities. "</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_10_paragraph1">"INCIFOR's research track record has led to advances in knowledge and innovation in the field of forensic science, as well as in the resolution of legal cases based on the analysis of various samples and biological remains. "</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_10_paragraph2">All these advances and research activities have positioned INCIFOR as an international centre of excellence in the field of forensic medicine and toxicology.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_11_paragraph0">INCIFOR\'s work not only contributes to solving cases, but also drives scientific advances in forensic medicine, toxicology, forensic genetics and criminology. Its work has a direct impact on justice, security and the training of highly qualified professionals.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_12_paragraph0">The Institute of Forensic and Criminological Sciences of Santiago de Compostela is a leader in scientific research applied to solving legal cases and, ultimately, improving public safety.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_14_title0">Forensic</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_14_title1"> Genetics</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_14_paragraph0">Here, DNA is analysed to identify individuals, establish kinship or solve crimes. They also work on identifying victims of disasters and studying ancient human remains.</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_15_title0">Forensic</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_15_title1">Toxicology</string>
    <string name="II_INCIFOR_miniscreen_15_paragraph0">Its activity focuses on the analysis of biological samples from living or deceased persons for the detection, identification and quantification of drugs, alcohol, poisons and all types of substances in the context of judicial investigations, such as homicides, accidents or cases of chemical submission. \nMany types of biological samples are analysed in its laboratory, in many cases revealing recent consumption and, in others, prolonged exposure over time to different types of substances, making it possible to establish a retrospective chronology of their consumption. This laboratory is constantly developing and publishing new analytical methods in influential scientific journals that improve the ability to detect and quantify new substances.\n</string>


</resources>